Open fridge.
Take chicken.
Close fridge.
Open package.
Take chicken.
Slice chicken.
Turn on stove.
Take chicken.
Slice chicken.
open cabinet
take oil
rinse hands
dry hands
put oil on pan
close bottle
place oil on cabinet
close cabinet
take pan
add chicken to the pan
take a spatula on pan
move chicken
Move chicken
Slice chicken
Add chicken
Put chicken on bin
Take knife and a slicing table
Move chicken
Take package
Remove plastic from package
Place plastic on bin
place food on bean
rinse package
trim plastic from package
place package in recycling box
place plastic on bean
rinse hands
move chicken
take fork
place fork on dishwasher
take knife
wash knife
Wash knife
Rinse knife
Place knife on dryer
Take slicing table
Rinse slicing table
Wash slicing table
Place the slicing table into the dryer.
Take a spatula
Move chicken
Turn of stove
[END SUBTITLE]